Balachowda Somu

Marketing Manager with 7+ years of experience in Sales and Marketing

Hyderabad, Telangana 500072 balachowda.grirmc@gmail.com +91 93935 51101

To work on challenging career and be a part of a progressive team that gives me opportunities to have a consistent growth in my learning curve and to utilize my skills for the ultimate growth of my team and the Organization.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Personal Details

Date of Birth: 1986-11-05 Eligible to work in: India

Industry: Construction, Marketing, Sales

Total years of experience: 7

Work Experience

Marketing Manager

Guru Raghavendra Infrastructures Pvt Ltd., - Tirupati, Andhra Pradesh December 2019 to January 2022

Need to search for the leads and convert into our customer by trying our best by explaining about the service, quality and reputation of the organization. And monitoring the supply and services which are going for current customers. And Maintaining the records and the dues to follow. Supply and collection was our duty as Marketing Manager.

Sales Manager

Vallabha feeds Pvt ltd., - Tamil Nadu, Karnataka, Chittor and Nellore. November 2014 to November 2019

Need to search for the leads by visiting the feed distributors and retailers and Convert them as our customers by explaining the quality of feed and the history of the organization. And need to maitain the consistency in the supply and services. The big task here was to hold the customer without any deviation to the other brands by maintaining the rapo with customers and by visiting frequently.

Education

Bachelor's in ECE

Anna University - Hyderabad, Telangana February 2022 to Present

Master's in MBA

University of Whales - Cardiff September 2010 to November 2011

Skills / IT Skills

• Ms Office

Languages

- Telugu, Expert
- Tamil Fluent
- English Fluent
- Hindi Intermediate

Certifications and Licenses

Driving Licence